Extremis is a documentary film directed by Dan Krauss.
A purely observational non-fiction film that takes viewers into the ethically
murky world of end-of-life decision making in a public hospital.
Herself, played by Monica Bhargava.
Herself, played by Jessica Zitter.
"Extremis" is a six-issue story arc from the comic book series Iron Man (vol.
4), published in issues one through six in 2005 and 2006 by Marvel Comics.
It was written by Warren Ellis and illustrated by Adi Granov.
Extremis elevates the status quo for Iron Man,
increasing the power of his armor significantly.
Extremis received mostly positive reviews, and it is often
listed as one of the best Iron Man stories.
Elements of Extremis were adapted for the 2008 film Iron Man, and the Iron Man: Armored Adventures episode
"Extremis," and the storyline serves as the primary source material for the 2013 film Iron Man 3.